<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Lagos Tour Guide</string>
    <string name="splash_screen_text">Welcome to LAGOS TOUR GUIDE</string>
    <string name="word_list_text">Open: </string>
    <string name="bogobiri_text">Bogobiri is located in the heart of Ikoyi, precisely at 9, 7 Maitama Sule Street, Lagos. Art lovers go to this place to have a good time and listen to live bands play invigorating music. Plays are also hosted here by Taruwa and on some nights, there is an open mic. If your date is an artsy person, this is one of the most exciting places that you can take them in Lagos.</string>
    <string name="freedom_park">This arts and recreation centre was built in 2010 to commemorate Nigeria’s 50th independence. It is also a cultural centre that was designed by architect, Theo Lawson. This is a good spot to bring someone who is interested in arts, culture and history. Many Afrocentric art shows are staged at this location.</string>
    <string name="foundry">The Foundry is a good place to go on a date in Lagos if you want to enjoy tasty meals and have an intimate conversation. It is located at 228B, Ajose Adeogun Street, Victoria Island Lagos. It has a cosy atmosphere and the booths are designed to seat at least two people on each side. Their impressive menu contains different interestingly named meals to soothe even the most selective palate.</string>
    <string name="ocean_basket">This Seafood restaurant has an extensive menu that contains whatever seafood delight you want. If your date loves seafood and a cosy ambience, this is one of the perfect spots to go to. Also, if you have never tried seafood before and want to be adventurous on this date, this is one of the best places to experiment with.</string>
    <string name="terra_kulture">Founded by Bolanle Austen-Peters in 2003, it has remained one of those establishments that cater to whatever artistic and recreational fantasies one might have. Their onsite restaurant has a variety of African and international dishes, they have a bookshop and an art gallery, a library, language school and theatre where plays are staged every Wednesday and Sunday.</string>
    <string name="pattaya">This is a serene spot to hang out and have a good time with that special somebody. It is located at 30, Adeola Hopewell, Victoria Island, Lagos. Asian and African dishes are both available on their extensive menu. The comfortable mahogany decor also helps you to relax better and take in the beauty of the moment.</string>
    <string name="ember_creek">Ember Creek Waterfront is a restaurant cum bar that transforms into an exciting and lively nightclub at night. It is located at 32, Awolowo Road, Obalende, Ikoyi, Lagos. If your date likes to dance to booming Afro-pop music, this is one of the safest and most lively bars to visit and get your groove on.</string>
    <string name="breenas_cafe">Breena’s Cafe is also located on the mainland. There are two branches. One at Maryland and other at Akoka. The address of the Maryland location is 19, Abbi Street, Mende, Maryland, Lagos while the Akoka branch is on Akoka Road, near St. Finbarr’s College, Yaba. If you and your date love pastry and tasty, spicy shawarma, Breena’s cafe is the plug for those food items.</string>
    <string name="dominos_pizza">Pizza, pizza and more pizza. Domino’s recently opened a branch in the Yaba area and this is the perfect date spot for university students who want to leave the school premises and do something extra. </string>
    <string name="cafe_neo">This is a cool coffee spot to go on a short date at. They have different outlets in Lagos but the favourites for young people are the one on the mainland at the E-Centre, Yaba and the one-off Sanusi Fafunwa Street, Victoria Island. They have a variety of coffee and health drinks and pastry that are of great value for their price.</string>
    <string name="belgian_rose">This is a very quaint cake shop at one of the busiest places in Lagos- Sabo. It is located at 318, Herbert Macaulay Way and is the perfect date spot to have an intimate conversation and tasty baked items on the mainland. The ambience helps you forget the noise and bustle going on outside the shop. Their goods are also very affordable and it is a family-owned bakery which was established in 2017.</string>
    <string name="maryland_mall">This new mall at Maryland hosts a lot of restaurants, bookstores, fashion and make-up stores and health lounges. it is located at 350 – 360, Ikorodu Road, Anthony Village, Lagos.  It is the cool new spot for youths and was established in 2016. It is a good place to have a full-day date. You can see a movie in one of the cinema halls, shop at Shoprite or one of the other stores, walk around and window shop, and get a bite to eat at one of the restaurants in the food court.</string>
    <string name="tarkwaBay">Tarkwa Bay is a lovely, aesthetically pleasing beach. It is a very romantic spot that is located near the Lagos harbour. There are so many outdoor activities to do like Horseback riding, speedboat riding and so on. If you are going out with someone that likes physical activity, this is a good spot to hang out. Just remember to wear light clothing and take a good camera for pictures.</string>
    <string name="releArtGallery">Located at 5, Military Street, Onikan Environment, Lagos. If your date is very interested in Contemporary art and aesthetics, Rele Art Gallery is one of the cool spots you can take them to see artworks. Time and again they host and feature creative artworks in their exhibitions.</string>

    <!--Drinks-->
    <string name="thePlace">The Place restaurant can be found in 3 locations in Lagos- Lekki, Victoria Island and Ikeja. At The Place, there is something for everyone. For the busy executive, the games room and its bar/lounge are open every day from 5 pm, offering a chance for workers to relax, unwind and avoid Lagos traffic! The Place is also popularly known for its exclusive tasty dishes which include Asun, grilled chicken and rice. On Fridays, the bar/lounge is transformed into a major night club with music from highly sought after DJs and A-list artists. The relaxed ambience and impressive service contribute to an overall enjoyable visit to The Place.</string>
    <string name="sailorsLounge">If you are looking for a lavish and pleasant nightlife experience, then Sailor’s Lounge is the place to visit. Located on Admiralty way in Lekki, it offers a perfect location for a relaxed evening after a long day at work. The tempo of the music is not so loud and boasts perfect views of the Lagoon. The sheer ambience is one that is rare to find in other spots in Lagos. If you are bored with the rumbling and booming of the clubs then this is a perfect place to head to.</string>
    <string name="bayLounge">Bay lounge has such an amazing vibe and ambience for a perfect evening outing in Lagos. It is a great place to visit when you are searching for a place to stay away from the ever-consistent Lagos traffic. From DJ sets to live jazz bands, there are so many fun activities like dining ‘al fresco’, movie nights, ‘live band’ and a discotheque with the Deejay spinning new and old school rhythms. Tucked in the swanky Lekki neighbourhood on Admiralty road, it is next to Sailors Lounge. If you get there between 6 pm and 7 pm then you will get to see the panoramic view of the beautiful Lagoon at your own pace.</string>
    <string name="rhapsodys">Lagosians love Rhapsody. Reasons! It is certainly one of the gorgeous places for night affairs. Located in Ikeja City Mall at Alausa, Ikeja, it has the perfect milieu for a long interesting evening if you are planning not to spend too much. Varieties speak when it comes to dishes, you will certainly rhapsodise over the perfectly made Nigeria classic “Prawn suya”.</string>
    <string name="beerHugz">In a finely dim and cosy setting, Bheerhugz is a stylish lounge, great for relaxing especially if you want to loosen up a bit. The cosy lounge makes you feel at home with the scrumptious meals prepared by the finest chefs in the industry, you will certainly enjoy their Redhugz menu which features delectable favourites like chicken, fish and roasted goat meat. Don’t forget to try the ” pork chops”, one of the best dishes on the menu. Located at Ikeja City Mall and Surulere, Bheerhugz is the place to enjoy a cool atmosphere and lovely view of the beautiful city of Lagos. Whether you are in Lagos or visiting soon, this place should be the number one on your list.</string>
    <string name="shaunzBar">Have an exciting evening in this bar with its electrifying atmosphere. It is a classic spot for all kind of minds and personalities seeking fun in music—did we mention that their karaoke nights are the best! You are bound to feel relaxed after staying for just 5 minutes. If you want to experience Lagos to its fullest, Shaunz Bar should be on your go-to list. Located at Sanusi Fafunwa in Victoria Island, Lagos.</string>
    <string name="seaLounge">This is the right place to be, you can relax, mingle and sip delicious cocktails while enjoying the calm seas and a variety of tasty bites to cater for every mood and palate. Located at Wole Olateju Crescent in Lekki. It is such a great place to visit with someone special. You can also take a sea cruise and enjoy your dinner while you are 20 miles away from the coast.</string>

    <!--Hotels-->
    <string name="bestWesternIslandHotel">Located at the ocean front in Victoria Island, Best Western Island hotel is a hotel for both business and leisure. The ocean front view presents a lovely panoramic view, giving guest a first class experience of all kinds of water sports. The rooms are all luxuriously designed and built for all categories of guest, with full service and modern day facilities. The cuisines are of a wide variety (local and continental dishes). The hotel has full well equipped fitness centre, restaurant, bar, outdoor swimming pool, cocktail lounge. Airport shuttles are readily available. The experience here is to be felt first hand. It’s a place like no other! Accommodation rates Rate: For as low as $190 per night</string>
    <string name="ekoHotel">Eko Hotels and Suites is a prestigious development of beautiful suites located at Kuramo waters, Adetokunbo Ademola Street in Victoria Island. This place echoes the glamour and style that offer the ultimate in luxury lodging. It boasts an elaborate luxurious interior, which is complemented with plush oriental style landscaped gardens with exquisite panoramic sea views giving a feeling of privacy and space. The rooms and suites are first-class, spotless and comfortable to suit all tastes. The restaurants are exceptional, exquisite food in great varieties (both foreign and local dishes). Facilities include deluxe 584 rooms, exquisite bar, conference hall, gym, spa and outstanding pool facing the ocean. The view from the room above is priceless, a sight to behold. Proudly African, the hotel has an African workshop that provides all forms of African arts and craft (metal and wood work). Accommodation rates: For as low as $410 per night</string>
    <string name="ellionHouse">Located in the heart of Ikoyi business district, The Elion House provides guests with boundless varieties of choice in terms of hospitality. The rooms are well furnished and designed to suit the taste of distinguished guests. The facilities include gym centre, conference halls, bar, lounge, and exquisite restaurant. The security system and services are compared to none. The foods come in great varieties, both local and continental dishes. Its peaceful, safe and a fun place to be. Accommodation rates: For as low as $240 per night</string>
    <string name="excellenceHotel">Nestled in the central district of Lagos mainland, precisely Ijaye – Isheri Road, Ogba-Ikeja; the hotel is a truly unique place to stay. The hotel is made of 71 well furnished rooms with all the state of art facilities for a hotel of its reputation. It is beautifully landscaped to compliment a massive structure of its kind. Hospitality is at its peak here; banqueting and outdoor catering services are tendered to both individuals and corporate bodies. Here they provide all kinds of facilities to suit guests such as restaurants, bar, lounge, security, Wi-Fi, 24hours electricity, outstanding outdoor pool, gym and many more. Accommodation Rates: For as low as $110 per night</string>
    <string name="federalPalaceHotel">Strategically situated in the heart of Victoria Island, just a walk from the Silverbird Galleria and a stone throw from the shores of the ocean, this place can be described as the commercial focal point of Lagos, a five star hotel and casino. The hotel caters for travellers with distinct taste and style and can be measured to any international standards. In terms of general hospitality, their services are impeccable. Depending on the rooms, the panoramic views from this hotel is priceless. Accommodation rates: For as low as $312 per night</string>
    <string name="fourPoints">Managed by Starwood, Four Points by Sheraton is located in Lekki Peninsula. The hotel’s extensive and well thought-out design makes it one of the most desirable places to stay in Lagos. It boasts spectacular views of the city and has superb facilities which include bars, coffee shops, lovely restaurants, spa, gym and many more. The facilities are well selected and equipped with high superiority; the rooms are immaculately decorated and more than adequately provisioned for the visitors. Good security is guaranteed and it’s a walk away from the Palms Shopping Mall in case you want to shop or watch a box office movie. If you are looking for a place like home, Four Points by Sheraton is one of the finest luxury hotels in Lagos. Accommodation rates: For as low as $326 per night</string>
    <string name="goldenTulip">The Golden Tulip is located in a vibrant trade and business districts in the heart of Lagos; precisely located at Amowo Odofin, Mile 2. The hotel provides visitors with a variety of business and leisure facilities, complimented by international service values and local sociable warmth. The hotel has a beautiful landscape, which spans across 7 hectares of tropical greenery and gardens. Facilities include variety of restaurants and bars, conference halls, banquet facility, gym and fitness centre, tennis courts, squash courts, array of shops and banks for visitors. Accommodation rates: For as low as $165 per night.</string>
    <string name="hotelBonVoyage">Located in the central area of Victoria Island, Hotel Bon-voyage is a beautiful place to stay, safe, serene and blissful. With luxury and affordable rooms that provide visitors with elegance and comfort in every way. The hotel is well-furnished with a stunning interior and offers with beautiful ocean views. Facilities include swimming pool, fitness centre, restaurants and bar. The cuisines are intercontinental (local and foreign dishes), tasty, lovely and spicy. It has an amazing view due to its location. It’s close to Kuramo Lake and directly opposite the Atlantic Ocean. At night it’s a beauty to behold. It really is a place to be! Accommodation rate: For as low as $205 per night.</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

</resources>
